-= www.OpenSubtitles.org =-
'Durga Ghat
India's North-East border'
'An unsolved community rival in a village'
We can't even enter the temples
Our children are not
allowed inside schools
So if we live in run-down
houses and wear shabby clothes...
Are we lesser beings?
Why do we still live this way?
Because they don't let us grow,
We're still their slaves
This school we're building...
...will be a slap on the face
to the people of upper caste
We are uneducated
At least let our
children go to school
Or we'll be crushed
under their tyranny forever
We shall unite against them!
They call themselves higher caste
What does that even mean?
Only they're allowed
to enter temples
So wearing this anklet
makes one superior?
I'm holding it now
If I wear this around my ankle,
am I one of them?
May I enter the temples now?
We must end this!
We shall not tolerate this anymore
In the name of caste, the ruthless massacre
of forty men women and children...
In the Uttarakhand massacre
that shook the country...
The Court have arrived at a verdict
At the end of the trial,
The Court finds the defendant...
...guilty
Go away!
'Chennai City Outskirts'
Hello?
I need to go to
the hospital urgently
-Can I hire a cab?
-Wrong number
-Is it Dass Travels? 2-4-1-
-Told you it's the wrong number!
Go to hell, man!
Such a bad start
Is there tea?
Yes, there is
What's the sticker for?
Dass Travels!
Oh and write down our
phone number and address...
Make it easier for the cops?
Take it down, fools!
-What's it?
-Tea, brother?
Two glasses
-Give it to me
-What's it?
Brother, he always gets
to wear the Inspector's uniform
-He never lets me have it
-Let it go, man
Bunch of kids...
You wore the Transport
Officer's uniform last week!
-What?
-Get lost
Caste Violence-Brutal slaughter of
40 members in Uttarakhand!
People still kill for
castes in North India, huh?
Want some tea?
Bring me a hot tea!
A package to Malaysia
is arriving from Pondicherry
You said someone's
coming to pick it up
Who is he?
He will be coming here, right?
Yes
What's his name?
He has no name
Is he God?
God can't drive cars
God can't drive cars!
Where's the car?
Who is he?
Why are you hurt?
Police!
Don't do this, Dass
Someone's life depends
on this package
You said he would
arrive sharp on time
Where is he?
-It's not time yet
-It's not time?
Only ten seconds to go
Now what?
Before you count to ten
Anything could happen
It's 7 o clock now
Where the hell are you guys?
He snatched the package away
Gather our men
Ask them to come, quick
-Isn't that the car?
-Looks like it
-Go...go I say
-Give some alms
That's him!
He is drinking tea over there
Get him! Quick
Stop him!
-Hello?
-Got the package?
Go on, catch him
I'll be waiting at the SMS Hotel
10 o' clock, sharp
Okay...okay
Do you know
what's in the box?
Okay, bye!
Hello, ma'am!
Look, I can't give you money
There's food in this pack
Bless you!
Hey...my beard
What's your problem with me?
How long do you plan on
playing the long haired side kick?
Send your boss over
"One plus one is two
Two plus one is three"
"Inside three it is four
Four, five, six"
"Six plus one is seven"
"Inside seven there is eight"
"Eight plus one is nine"
"Nine plus one is ten"
Careful
"Before counting ten..."
"This hunting is for killing"
"The den of tiger"
"Will he cross the gate?"
"You change your route"
"The jungle of lion"
"If that one goat..."
"You try to steal"
"You won't cross the border"
"Before counting ten..."
"I'm waiting for the cruise
He is going to be on the news"
"There is nothing funny
Let me free bunny"
"On the street no one can survive,
don't play with this man"
"He can take you for a ride"
"There is no way to stop him
He'll move like a fire"
"Everything will get shattered"
It was like a 3D car chase
Went VROOM, over my head
'Happy birthday to you'
Cheer for our starlet!
On behalf of Mother Teresa
Women's Hostel
-Click a picture
-Click a good one
We present you this plastic
box on your birthday
Make us look good
-I have to show this to groom
-Have you clicked, sis?
Don't move
Come closer
To the left
Don't smile so much
-My right
-Okay
"On seeing he looks young"
"Go carefully brother"
"Don't touch the electricity charged wire"
"He can face anyone single handedly"
"A vehicle without brake"
"If you come nearby, it'll bang"
"There is no match to him"
"He'll overcome you"
"Hey, six rivers, seven mountains..."
"He'll come around all eight directions"
He's behind us now!
Who is chasing whom here?
"Before counting ten..."
"My life is like a race
I kick my way"
"There is no dearth to
happiness Enjoy it"
"I'm waiting for the cruise
This is going to be on the news"
"Show me the way
Everybody come with me"
"There is nothing funny
Let me free bunny"
"On the street no one can survive"
"My life is like a race
I kick my way"
"There is no dearth
to happiness...enjoy it"
You, rascal!
"This is fire
An electricity wire"
"The rope of Yama
On touching you'll lose life"
"This is real tower
Move away"
"Now you'll know his real power"
Stop...stop
"Before counting ten..."
'Before counting ten...'
He came in here
-Close the shutters
-Okay
Wait!
There were seven cars
Say four men in a car...
4 times 7 makes 28
Let's do a head count
2,3, 10...24!
So who is missing?
Oh
The blue car went swimming, eh?
And?
Oh my god!
It's the police
Won't you change clothes?
The chase is over
Is there a problem, brother?
Okay, take it
Oh! It's food
I'll take it
Where is the 'holy stuff'?
Holy stuff?
Is that your code word
for the goods?
The other day, one guy used
the code word 'Fried Chicken'
I thought he meant-
-Hear something?
-Where is it?
It was delivered at 10 o clock
I'm all about punctuality
Show him your watch
See?
It's 10:10
We've been chasing you for an hour!
You weren't really looking
You, rascal!
Thank you
This was my fee
Take it if you want
But I'll finish at least four of you
What day is it?
At least four of you
Who's coming first?
Who wants to be my starter?
You? Or you?
You...you're last
Where are you from?
What's your name?
I'm Gates
Bill Gates
Catch him
So I looked at him, right?
I swerved the steering
The car just drifted around
I wanted to shake that guy up,
but he's telling them bedtime stories
I thought it's all over...
What's he doing?
Counting the money for him
Come here, he was like this
And I was here...
But I didn't budge!
I went like this
And got through!
That was that
The client was happy, I was happy
I took my fee and was off
Then why did you quit?
Can't work for a mistrustful employer
who thinks you're stealing fuel, right?
-That's true
-He's got dignity
#NAME?
Then I drove an ambulance
in Nungambakkam for a while
That lasted six months
An ambulance, too?
That explains your
antics behind the wheel
Green tea is for the man
He just got here
What's happening?
I've added honey
Is that okay?
That's fine
Can you check on the food?
I smell something burning
I smell it too
But someone's getting burnt here
You make money in such means
What do you do with the money?
I'm asking you
Why is he getting so emotional?
I have a little sister
Once while going in the car,
there was an accident
It was my mistake
So I make money by any means;
All for my sister
She was hit on the back of
her head and she fell into a...
A coma!
Yes, how did you know, brother?
Been seeing it in movies
You should come with me
Want me to drop you somewhere?
I'm saying, come with me
Let's do 'jobs' together
What jobs?
Like, I came in the morning
The package was exchanged
And then we fought
-I'll check and tell you
-Check and tell?
Listen to me
What's wrong with him?
He's taking my apprentice away!
Dass Travels
Hmmm, okay
Okay
Okay?
Brother, working for
a boss doesn't work for me
Just tell me when
there's a job, I'll do it
This is what
they're talking about?
Finished counting?
What did he ask?
He asked if Dass was
related to Lord Labough Dash
There's 100 in this bundle
But only 98 in this
How they cheat us!
Here, that makes it 100!
I'm off!
Here, keep it
Bye!
Hey, give me your phone number
I'll call you when a job comes up
Phone number?
Hey, Police costume
Your name?
Wonder what he'll
call himself this time
Where is she hiding?
She is not in room
Where has she gone?
It's my fault, letting you stay here
Two months since she paid the rent
Tell her to meet me
when she's back
What?
Saw a cockroach, madam
Who knows when you'll find
a good job and pay me my rent?
Women drivers wanted at
airport to drive battery cars
Great pay!
-As soon as I get my license...
-You need to learn driving first
-What's the package worth?
-Two big ones
I know a guy
I'll check
-Bond?
-Who is it?
It's me, Dass
Dass? Brother! Tell me
A jeep needs to be brought
from Pondicherry, you'll do it?
No, brother
I'm at work now, I will...
It's a valuable package, man
I can't just send anyone
You said you'd work for me;
But you keep backing out
I called you because
it's an important task
-I'll pay you good
-Pondicherry?
How far from here?
Consider it done
If you can drive this,
you can drive a real car
Sit down
Sit
It's just like a normal car
What about the stick here?
No gears on this car
But you'll find everything else
The steering, controls...
Don't be afraid
-The one on the left is the brake
-Isn't that the accelerator?
I know to drive-
Look at that!
Nut case!
Take your hands off!
Look at that face
7...8...9...10
Okay, I'm off!
-Brother?
-Come here
-Is it ready?
-Ready
Brother!
He's not left? Hide it
What's this?
You're earning so much
But look at what you've paid me!
Look, this note is torn
Okay
You scared me!
Who is this guy?
Never seen him here before
He's new
What's his name?
Oh no! Never ask for his name
"On asking name you are irritating"
"Tell the truth who are you?"
"Taking fees you are confusing"
"If I rush it is bullet
Danger is like chicklet"
"I'm a car driving flight jet
I'm a magnet for girls"
"There is no cage for me"
"Why there is so much
anger in your heart?"
"Pray what you want
My name is Bond"
Your name?
Bond
James Bond
"On asking name you are irritating"
"Tell the truth who are you?"
"Taking fees you are confusing"
"There is no fear in my eyes
There is no one to my level"
"For everyone I'm a pet
To the enemy I'm a nuisance"
"There is no fence to me
Till I play it is jolly"
"On hitting everything
will get destroyed"
"My name is Kohli"
"Kohli Virat Kohli"
'Virat Kohli hits a six'
She was right here
Don't know where she's gone?
She just disappeared
We've come here on a picnic
from Mother Teresa Ladies Hostel
We were a group of 40
The other 39 have lost their way
I am safe
She lost her way
but blaming us
Go, get her
"On asking name you are irritating"
"Tell the truth who are you?"
"Taking fees you are confusing"
"My home town is Paramakudi
Find out who I'm"
"I know all the tricks
Learn it from me"
Who are you?
"For learning I didn't
go for tuition"
"But in acting I'm an ocean"
"Something new is my fashion
My name is Haasan"
"Haasan...Kamal Haasan"
"Are you a good
or bad person?"
"Dance...dance"
Come on dance
"Rock...rock"
'Somewhere in North India'
Was it you?
You clicked this photo?
I clicked it at an event in Chennai
Do you know anything else about her?
I don't know
Do you have hard copies?
I gave all the hard
and soft copies to him
Ajay!
Everything's in order, brother
So
What's your fee?
It's your wish
What's this?
It's that girl's
-Why haven't you sent it, yet?
-We just got the address
We cut it an hour back!
If her father doesn't pay up,
tell him we'll chop off her hand
-Hello, Dass?
-Sir?
Can't hear him
Tell me, brother
I'll e-mail you a photograph
Okay, sir
Do a background check
Like last time?
Just collect the details
I'll tell you what to do
Scan these photographs
and mail them to Dass's ID
So
-Has anyone else seen these?
-Absolutely not
Only you
Good! No one will
get to see it
What?
Blade
He's a good friend of mine
I'll introduce you to him
Sure
Blade, meet my friend
What is this?
Blade
Darling, squeeze a bit of lemon and
add some salt to this orange punch
It tastes heavenly
-We've got a mail
-Already?
Yes, a girl's photo
No student has failed a test,
ever since my father's time
Be seated
Your instructor will be here
Why have you
lined up all the photos?
Why so many photos?
I take a new photograph
each time I apply for driver's license
Oh So?
She's only failed 14 times till now
This would be the 15th attempt
But I'll surely pass this time!
You've come to the best driving school
You will pass hundred percent
I already know because I'm
wearing my lucky colour maroon
But you wore the same colour when
you failed at the Anna Nagar center
That was in March
My lucky colour was green then
Right
Morning, Boss
This is your instructor
-Hello, sir!
-Sit down
Have we met before?
I have
The other day
You'll attend 15 classes totally
3, 500 rupees
-Your name?
-Shakeela
Why not? Can't people be
named after adult movie stars?
What's your mum's name?
Parangimalai Jyoti?
Boss!
How did you know?
But not Parimala
She's from
Viralimalai, near Trichy
Sis!
They're teasing you
-What's your name?
-Ratnam
Mani Ratnam
Your address?
4/3 Barathidas third cross street
Manapakkam
There's a cemetery right
next to this ladies' hostel
This girl lives here
Have you collected
all the details?
No politicians or police
connection in her family?
No such thing
So we'll take the job?
Wow...! Next job
Did you check the birthmark?
A mole on the right ear
Yes, it's here
This is the right girl, huh?
She's feisty
I'll kill you
Let us go
Who is this hero?
Why is he getting so excited?
He's her boyfriend
Send him away
I've told you,
I don't like extra baggage
You can't get away with this
I'll kill you!
What does he want?
Wants to hit me and save the girl?
Ask him to come
Go on
No!
-Sir, I've got all her details
-Tell me
Her name is Shakeela
Works in a beauty salon
She's from Trichy
Doesn't have a father
Mother lives in their hometown
She's been living
here for 7-8 years now
Where?
Mother Teresa
Working Women's Hostel
Room number 407
She looks like
It's 401
IT'S 4-0-1!
Is it '1'?
Make this girl shut up
Sorry, Brother just missed a line
What if someone missed
a line while shaving your neck?
This is an important job
Don't know if you can do it
-What needs to be done?
-Need to kidnap that girl
The girl needs to
reach here by the 23rd
Your salary will be ten million
Okay, brother
-The girl should be safe
-I'll make sure!
Be careful
Guys, where are you?
Where is everyone?
We've hit a jackpot!
Morning, sir!
6 to 8 are auspicious hours today
So I came early
S. Saravanan!
PR
Priya!
Sha Kee
Get in
Be careful
Don't worry!
I was talking to him
God, I hope everything goes well
What?
You'll be driving the car...not God
Okay, shall we start?
Take a look at these three mirrors
This is the triangle of driving
Golden!
Golden triangle of driving
We must always pay attention to it
Okay?
Similarly, this is the ABC of driving
Accelerator...Brake
Clutch
Must bring it to neutral
Safety first!
Put on your seatbelts
Then
Press the accelerator very,
very gently
And when it starts moving
Use the same leg for
brake and accelerator
If the Instructor says to stop the car,
you must turn on the indicator
And then bring your hand here
And then slowly brake
Oh no!
You hit the brakes and stop
-Thank you
-Shall we start?
Should I put on the hand brake?
Turn off your mouth
and turn on the ignition
Actually, sir
It's enough if I can
drive like you do
By when can you teach me that?
The others have paid, too!
You do all the talking
-What?
-Be quiet
Why do you get worked up?
We're here to learn
Don't ask me...Ask her
He keeps putting me down
How can I do it?
A teacher should give extra
attention to weak students!
She honks even at speed breakers!
You said to honk
if something comes in the way
Speed breakers can't hear, ma'am
Listen, I can teach anything
But I can't teach her driving
I can't cook! Teach me to cook?
Should have run you
over with the car
Named after director Mani Ratnam
But such loud dialogues!
I thought his name
was Sunil Gavaskar?
-Just do this for me, dear
-No way!
He's just a driver
Shows off like he's a pilot
Get going, 'di'
Did you just call me 'di'?
Talk to me like that again,
I'll turn your face around
Let it go, sis
If you call me 'di',
I'll call you 'da'
I've paid 3,500 rupees
If you won't teach me,
let's go to court now
To run and hide in
your house on the way?
WHERE IS MY CAR?
Why are you looking up?
Who parked the car up there?
He asked me to start
the car and switch gears
I switched gears before starting
This is the first and last time
Your wrecked my car!
Now you act like a schoolgirl?
That car was my family's legacy!
I will take you to court
Sir, don't get mad
You took my money
Now get me a license
You gave me your word
You said 100% pass
Is that it?
Okay
I'll even beg the RTO
to get her a license
Just don't ask me
to teach driving
Okay
-I like this deal
-What deal?
Okay, I'll see you tomorrow
Bye!
That's a fancy number!
Actor Ajith used this
car in the movie 'Billa'
Really? Cool
So the cops will go after Billa
Remove it
Good job on the car
We'll kidnap the girl in this car
Our lives are set after this job
-What's with the new coat?
-Cost me 7,500
-That feels tough
-I've been working out
That's so unnecessary
All you need is a small surgery
You're always taking notes
What's your ambition?
I want to learn the trade from you,
and become a great gangster!
Really?
Then I'll become a politician
And enter the field of cinema!
-You want to become an actor?
-No, a producer
Producer?
My prayers are with you
I'll be driving...not God
What's with the green clothes?
I'm going on a date...with my guy
Look over there
How is that?
Bye, sis...I'll share
pictures on WhatsApp
Hi!
Looks like Mani Ratnam is still angry
-Morning, sir!
-That's a big note
That's my girl
Your girl? You're in love?
Yes, one-sided, though
-What?
-I don't
-But she likes me
-Doesn't matter
I'll give her a license
if she passes the test
-That's not her thing
-What?
I mean, it's a Tuesday
Not her day
Let her drive on Wednesday,
then I'll give her the license
Sir! Officer
Why...?
-Manikandan sir?
-That's me
You're right
I'll clear the test
and collect my license
She's creating a scene!
What scene?
What a drama queen!
Look, sir
My poor mother
She is a housemaid
She's struggling every day
Her daughter has attained
a marriageable age
I must get a license, find a job
Earn some money and
buy gold for her wedding
-Poor thing!
-You have a sister?
No, I'm the only daughter
I was talking about me
Look, sir I believe in hard work
-So I will drive now
-Correct
She wants to work hard
-Let's go?
-Let's go
He's a goner
Drive straight towards me
-I'll give you a license
-Okay sir
She's an expert at running over
He's her target now!
What?
Shakeela!
How did you know my name?
The accident last week...
...at the Nungambakkam
Road Transport Officer Office?
He's admitted in the hospital now
Room 402
I sent him a bouquet
Not a bouquet
It was a funeral wreath!
He's not coming back
Shakeela, do you know
how to reverse?
That's really easy
Just back up 5 meters
Or even 5 feet
I'll issue your license
Okay, sir
Let's go!
I want to take one
last look at that guy
I'm ready
Hello!
Oh no
I switched to the first
gear instead of reverse
Manikandan sir!
Oh no!
Thank god, the helmet is okay
What a girl!
She sent the Road Transport Officer
on his final road trip
There's the Ladies' Hostel
Yeah, it's there to my left
The main road is right here
Yes
No, it's quiet here
Yeah, okay
The road looks empty
I'm near the cemetery
-That's the girl?
-Yes
She looks average
Why is she worth 10 million?
Just do your job, get your money
-Shut up, now
-You said it, brother!
Stay on the line, brother
Madam, do you know this address?
Show me
All okay here
Dubai Cross street?
I don't know the address
Tell me one more time?
Yes, I did straight and left
I'm here at the place
-Yes, brother?
-Very good, man
No issues?
No issues, brother
Where to bring her?
Who is bringing her?
Billy
The one who got the package
from Kolkata last time
That guy!
Give Billy my number
He needs to come to Mussoorie,
Uttarakhand
He must call me once
every three hours
-Okay, brother
-At any cost
I'll take care
-I want the girl here by the 23rd
-Okay, brother
If you fail,
you shall die on the 24th
What?
Got it?
What was that noise?
It's nothing
Everything's okay
Take care!
-Text me Billy's number
-Okay, brother
It's the cops, brother
The windows are tinted
They can't see us
Lift her!
Into the trunk
Cover her with something
Quick!
Won't stop the car?
Be quiet, I'll deal with it
Roll down the windows
Down, I say
How I help you?
Why did you take the keys?
Hello, Traffic Control room...over!
Traffic Control South 22
We've seized the vehicle
Sir
It's the one we were looking for
Sir, listen to me
He sped away in Mylapore
We've caught him at Nandanam junction
Send for the tow vehicle
You refuse to stop the vehicle,
and now you're arguing with a cop?
What's funny?
You chased us for this?
We're toiling under the sun
and you break the rules
And speed away in an imported,
air conditioned car?
It's not imported, just painted!
Who said it's imported?
Sir, we know the Commissioner
What's his name?
-I think it's Walter Vetrivel
-Listen
Come straight to the
Commissioner's office
Pay the fine, learn his name,
and then take your car
Officer, please
I said I'll deal with it!
Who asked you to talk
about the Commissioner?
-Get out of here!
-Let's go
Where are you taking my car?
Stop...stop
-I said stop
-You deal with the Officer
The girl is in the trunk
-Make the call
-Call who?
That guy, what's his name
Hello, Bond?
Called me first thing
in the morning
-Who?
-Shakeela
Daughter of Jyothi
What does she want?
She wants a refund
'Cause we didn't get her license
The fool wants her money back
She's no fool!
You're wrong, Boss
She speaks to the point
Why are you staring
at that vehicle?
See that blue car?
There's a small job
Totally 6 cars
It's in the middle
It's parked wrong side
Okay
'The Earth rotates around it's
own axis and revolves around the Sun'
I remember my geography now
-Brother?
-Bond!
The vehicle is up on the first floor!
What?
The first floor!
The car is not registered
Nor insured
Don't let the cops get to it
There's a package
worth 10 million!
Commissioner Office?
How far?
"One plus one is two
Two plus one is three"
"Inside three it is four
Four, five, six"
What are you going to do?
See that blue car?
We're picking it up
You make it sound like
picking up clothes on discount
How many signals in this route?
A police booth here
One way traffic on the left
And a bridge over here
"This hunting is for killing"
"The den of tiger"
"Will he cross the gate?"
"You change your route"
"The jungle of lion"
"If that one goat..."
"You try to steal"
"You won't cross the border"
"Before counting ten..."
"On seeing he looks young"
"Go carefully brother"
"Don't touch
the electricity charged wire"
"He can face anyone single handedly"
"A vehicle without brake"
"If you come nearby, it'll bang"
"There is no match to him"
"He'll overcome you"
"Hey, six rivers, seven mountains..."
"He'll come around
all eight directions"
"Before counting ten..."
Bond!
Brother, I've got the car
You're James Bond, alright I knew it
I'll bring it to the garage?
No, no, no
No, we've given this
address to the cops
Where are you now?
Pallavaram Railway Station
I hear the police siren
-Just a lone cop
-Is he following you?
Working hard for his measly salary!
In that case take the national highway
to the State of Andhra Pradhesh
-We can't have cops at our tail
-Brother, you said it's a quickie
No way!
Listen to me
I'm wearing my shorts now
You look great!
No way
The siren is getting louder
Why did you stop?
Send someone else to pick up the car
The package is in the car!
We're dead men if
I have other work, brother
I was going to send Billy,
but there was this incident
Look, there's no fuel!
You just don't listen
There's money on
the dashboard, take it
-I have work to do now
-What do you want?
I don't want it
-I'll give you fifteen
-Fifteen?
Why are you laughing?
Hi!
It needs to reach Mussoorie
Take it there
-Mussoorie
-Get down
How far?
Stop
Your voicemail was
in Telugu language
What's this place?
This place is my owner's property
Being cocky?
You caught me
Tell me, what is this place?
This is Renigunta
Boss, I'm on a delivery job
I'll be back in two days
You're taking the car
we just snatched?
Yes
They've offered fifteen grand
I'll get it done
Wow Fifteen?
What's so special about that car?
They're the kind who
smuggle diamonds in car tyres
I'll just do my job
You've snatched it
from the cops, be careful
Okay
Sir?
Fill up the tank for 500 rupees
Full tank for 500?
My battery is dying
I'll finish my job and call you
Oh! He meant 5 of those 500s
Sir, got some water to drink?
There's a motel right there
You'll find something
hot and spicy to eat
Check the air, too
Okay
There's a girl in the motel
Watch out for that one
She'll strip your shirt away
Escape!
-What happened?
-Sorry!
The food wasn't good?
Much worse
Much worse?
Just don't sing
Why is he running so fast?
Madam
Hello?
Excuse me
Okay
No one seems to care!
I'm the one who
swallowed the ghost itself
"I must drive vehicle
and go far away"
"I'm extremely hungry here"
"Get something hot
and spicy fast"
"Hot and spicy
hot and spicy"
"Poor fellow
He has got trapped"
"Why do you want to do
unnecessary acts, dear?"
"You are stepping into danger,
are you crazy?"
"Now also you can run away"
"Else become a member
in our association"
You wanted spicy?
Eat it
It was hot, alright
But where's the spice?
Look over there
"Gaana...Gaana Telanganaa..."
"I'm a hot spicy chilli"
"I'm a beauty who'll charm anyone"
"Just by seeing me saliva
will drip from mouth"
"If you touch me with mouth
tears will come out of eyes"
"All the guys are just useless"
"They are the beeda chewed
and spit by girls"
"The tongue has become red"
Eat the chilli and you win
Good luck, gentleman
Watch now
"Gaana...Gaana Telanganaa..."
"Has he come to control you all?"
"Has he come to free us?"
Second round!
Those are the rules
-Really?
-Yes!
Super!
"Gaana...Gaana Telanganaa..."
"She is a candle that will melt in fire"
Nobody here?
Saw that? He's got
a foreign car and everything
It's not imported, man
It's been altered
It's cash!
Come, look here
These are the gun's spare parts
The person who assembles it first,
wins the bullet to shoot
Time starts now!
"Where has he come from?
Has he come to love you?"
"Fix it fast Tighten the screws
Assemble it fast and win over her"
"He is mess up and
do something"
What has happened this?
Who fired the bullet?
Is she dead?
You have won
-I won't agree
-I will kill you
She looks like a muffin!
Wake up, sweetheart
First I found a phone, then cash
And now a girl!
Let me go first, please?
I'll make it quick
You only saw her first
Brother is on the way
No way!
You can't always have it your way
Let me go first this time
I'll go first
Selvam! Catch her
"He is attacking me
with bullet less gun"
"Gaana...Gaana Telanganaa..."
"This Sultana is born to win"
"Masatana has come to charm me"
"Without knowing about
you I asked for address"
"Without finishing the game I lost to you"
"It is my pass time
to take others for ride"
"You made me flat,
lift up your collar"
"You are the talk of the town"
"Gaana...Gaana Telanganaa..."
"Is he the head for everyone?"
Why is she getting into
the same car she came in?
"Has he come to free us"
And they say I am crazy!
She came this side
Hey, where have you gone?
The fuel station, brother
I thought they'd strip you,
but you ended up making them strip!
Mani Ratnam!
-Try that the next time
-Okay, I'll be back
Look over there
A blue car is coming
to your way, stop it
Hey!
Look at that!
The chick is in the car
Gentlemen, excuse me
-What is this?
-First, come outside
Don't touch the car
You're a fraud yourself,
and you're telling us?
Who, me?
Just come out!
-Running away?
-Hey, loose
Hi, sir
What are you doing
in the car, fool?
They chased me, I didn't
know it was your car I hid inside
Sir!
Mani Ratnam, sir!
-What?
-Save me
That's not me
The car is okay I am off!
Just move!
If they'd touched my car
that's a different story
You don't know this guy at all
You don't know what
he can do once he's angry
Idiot, get down
-Dare to touch me now?
-Get down
Come on, come on
-Be quiet, idiot
-I'm warning you
Not to save myself
But to save you from him
Brother, punch her in the mouth
What's this?
She's getting rescued
by her kidnapper!
Sir! Leave the weapons in the car
-Weapons?
-Don't get mad
Hello
Dare to touch now?
Get down
You...?
You don't always
get to block the way
10 20 30 40
He says he'll knock down
one man before the count of ten
So you do the math
-He is some hero, huh?
-When did I say that?
You can't do all the talking
Let me talk, too
Hello! One minute
You've smashed the headlights
Pay 10 bucks each for the bulb,
I'll be on my way
I have nothing to do with the girl
I'm telling you-
9-Aug
Sir, make him understand
Just smash him
It's gone
-Time for a catch punch?
-Say it
You smashed his bulb,
he smashed yours!
Go...go
You know each other?
Yes, quite well
-Now I get it
-Get what?
You and him are
He's looking!
Hey, hit me
Count to ten now
No, small-
No, please don't
Sir, be patient
Let's talk it out
I'll count for you
7, 8, 9,10
Hey, where is Mussoorie?
About 3500 kms from here, brother
It will take three days to reach?
But our man will
get there in two days
He doesn't know the girl
is in the trunk right?
-Okay, call him up
-Okay, brother
Call for you
-Hello?
-Billy?
You son of a
Pass the phone to Dass
Who is it?
Hello!
Dass, what are you doing?
The car should have
left two hours back
But Billy is answering the landline!
-What's going on there?
-I've sent another man
Who gave you the rights
to change the driver?
He takes two days where
other will take three
He's superb, brother
-What's his name?
-James Bond
Dass, are you kidding me?
Isn't it Sunil Gavaskar?
-He said Michael Jackson
-No, Mike Tyson?
Well, its
Give me his phone number
It's 95
0-0-4
Dial this number
Call him, quick...quick
Before Pooran Singh calls him
Quick, call him
Who is calling?
-Hello!
-I am Dass
Dass the electrician?
My fuse is blown
Can you fix it?
-It's not broken
-The girl?
She went with the driver
The kidnapper is the rescuer?
I don't even understand this plot!
-Hang up, man
-Hello?
What's happening?
-Hello, Bond?
-Hello?
Who are you, Sir?
This is Pooran Singh
Who are you?
You're Poor and you Sing?
Where's the girl?
You can ask me
in Hindi or Tamil
The girl is gone
You understand?
What's he blabbering?
Hey, switch off the phone
Hello?
It was busy a while back,
and now it's switched off!
What's happening?!
Son of a
Come here!
Something's wrong
Dass is not answering the phone
You start immediately
Everyone in
Billy, something's not right
You go in the same route
I'll call you back
One second
Blade, go with him
-Ajay
-Bro!
-We have to get this right
-Don't worry
Massacre in Uttarakhand
Death penalty for
the killer of 40 people
Don't know why they
tried to kidnap me
Look, I'm travelling
on an important task
You can't tag along
I've got an important job, too
I can't go with you, either
Drop me at a phone booth
Would the girl be conscious now?
Of course
It's been hours now
James Bond was her
driving instructor
You're telling me now?
They knew each other already!
You ran the background check
Hit you
Idiot!
We've filled their tank, given him a bundle
of money and sent them on a fun trip
So I'm a pimp here?
Billy?
The girl had regained consciousness
The two had left together
Billy
Kill him
Then you drop the girl
Bring me good news
after delivering her!
Go now
Boy! Look for Pajero
320 headlights
What?
There's a bus to Chennai from here
But money for ticket
Think I'm a beggar?
Return my money
What?
Your money?
What money?
You took my money
But you didn't get me a license
Nor did you teach me driving
I paid 3500 as single payment
Give it back to me
Return it!
Shouldn't have picked
her up in my car
I didn't need your car
Here
Brat
Hello?
Hello, ATM?
This is Shakeela
Where did you go, sis?
I was kidnapped by four men
They tried to misbehave
Really? I'll come join you
We'll have fun
Your stories won't work with me
You're loafing around
with your hostel rent due!
Look, it'll take me a day
or two to get back
-Don't wait up
-Where are you going?
Going on an important
mission to Mussoorie
With the instructor
Who? That foul-mouth
from the driving school?
-Don't talk about him like that
-Looks like you're switching lanes
-No such thing
-Don't feel shy
Listen
I'll be back in a few days
Don't look for me
The hostel rent?
I can't hear you
I call you back
Sis!
Hello?
"You are the talk of the town now"
Oh no!
Sir
You can't drive in
the hills without headlights
Give me money to buy a new bulb
-One minute
-Make it quick
I gave her all my money
And fought with her, too
Only way out is the
mother tongue we share
You Tamil Me Tamil
Why fighting?
What?
I thought about it
You keep the money
Teach me driving
This is even worse
I'll come with you
No I need to travel far
It'll take me three days
You can teach me in two days
-I'll manage
-Two days, huh?
'Same time at Uttarakhand'
-What are you doing?
-I'm studying, mom
Okay, eat up
And this is your target
What's this?
This is the safety lock
This is called trigger
Got it?
Trigger!
If you pull the trigger,
it fires a bullet
And this is how you aim
When you pull
No! You have to take aim
Aim for your target,
and pull the trigger
Don't hurt my daddy!
Spare my child
You can kill me
Off target by a little
Need to waste another bullet now
Don't hurt my daddy
We should have killed these
two along with those forty
They need to be nipped at the bud
No one left to sprout now
Want me to sleep here?
No, I'll sleep here
You get a room at a five
star or a three star hotel
Pest!
I'm worried about the bulb
not getting fixed till morning
And you're nagging me
Don't have any money
What?
I'm hungry
Because the alarm went off?
No, the alarm went off
because I'm hungry
God!
You!
They have kidnapped you...
...but let free
I have to punish them
You can't satisfy
a woman's hunger
Call yourself a man?
Excuse me?
Hunger!
Not that kind of hunger
This is different
What are you doing?
Let me go!
Where is he?
He went to North India for your job
Does he have any family?
Tell me
Mother?
Father?
Or a sister?
Brother, look at this cover
What?
I thought I saw a ghost
Ghosts can't affect other ghosts
You said you were hungry
Here
Idiot! Cost me two bucks
Can't even eat a biscuit right?
Sorry-
Here
Went out in the pouring
rain to get it
What a waste!
When you get mad,
your eyes squinch
It's nice
I'm cursing you here
We're in North India
South Indian curses don't count
Go on!
What is this?
Tell me
Whose medicines are these?
-Tell me
-It's mine
Then drink it!
Is your name Nandini?
Who is Nandini?
May you prosper!
May your siblings attain
great heights and prosper
You went in the dark all alone?
Weren't you scared?
Yeah, right
I can tell by the way you drive
You've never been
in an accident?
They say you develop a fear
if you meet with an accident
-But you are...
-Once
Just once
And after that one time
I lost all fear
Bus or auto?
What did you crash?
Next time, call a cab
Understand?
I can't keep driving you around
Think I'm jobless?
What are you doing?
Gloves! I made it
myself in craft class
Put it on
You said you felt discomfort
while driving, right?
Thank you
Who are you messaging this late?
Not messaging
It's WhatsApp
Who is it?
That skinny boy?
How do you know him?
He's the one who 'likes'
all your lame Facebook pictures
Brother! Why are you going
through my Facebook page?
I'm your older brother, 'di'
Call me 'di' again,
I'll turn your face around
Call me 'di'
and I'll call you 'da'
I' m a major now
There's an hour to
go for your birthday
Brother!
You remembered?
Cake!
-What?
-Wish me
Some guy would call you at 12,
and say he wanted to wish you first
I don't want to compete with that
What did you say?
Here
You brat!
Head-
It hurts, brother
Brother, don't do-
It's hurting, brother
I should've be more careful
It was my fault
Excuse me!
A few bills are pending
Look at this, Mother
Slept well?
Yeah, we stayed up
late talking last night
Saw the keys?
The keys?
The driver always has the keys
Don't ask me
Called me a driver?
One who drives the car is a driver
Hey...shut up
Men are always like this
You misplace things around the house
and expect women to find them
Women are always like this
You're all sweet in the night
and you sulk in the morning
Go stuff yourself with food!
Are Mr and Mrs
Mani Ratnam fighting
Early morning
Who said we're a couple?
She told me you loved each other
She's lying
I'm not Mani Ratnam
My name is Dass
A.R.Muruga Dass
Oh darn!
It was in my pocket all along?
I'll plant it on her
That's better
Give me the keys
We need to leave, it's late
I told you to look in the car
I don't know
Look in your pocket
It should be there
I told you I don't have it
Won't you look first?
What are you doing?
-Let me go!
-It's here
What are you doing?
Sorry
By mistake-
Your name suits you
How long will you take
to make a call?
I called-
"This kind of intoxication is
not good for you heart"
"Even on leaving it'll stand and smile
This craziness won't leave"
I was hungry
You went and ate without me?
"The way I like, this world is
full of beauty in front of me"
Fuel for 52 rupees and 50 paise!
Don't answer!
-Check the number
-It's STD call
Must be Pooran Singh
I told you to switch off the phone!
"Tell me why are you
dancing, heart?"
"This kind of intoxication is
not good for you heart"
"Even on leaving it'll stand and smile
This craziness won't leave"
Ate something else without me?
Get lost!
"He is coming to steal the heart"
"Put a piece of your shawl on me"
Pandey
Chulbul Pandey
Quality Inspector
No sand in the fire buckets?
Why is madam seated on the floor?
Get a chair, quick
Nothing is in order here
Okay, how much is it?
Who're you trying to bribe?
I'm Chulbul Pandey!
We'll be back
"I'll remain beside you
I'll wonder seeing you"
"Whether you say or not I'll stop"
"Daily there is an auspicious sign
This is a new journey"
"This path must take
me to my destination"
"Whole my life I was alone"
"This loneliness must end
You came for that..."
Think that's funny?
Brother, I've posted men
at all the toll gates on the way
They haven't crossed the town
They've crossed this toll gate
We're checking each
and every toll gate
-The tank is empty
-Yes, it's empty
Pocket is empty, too
I'm starving
Me too
What to do now, Mani Ratnam sir?
Nope
Hood
Robin Hood
We take what we need
You're saying we steal?
"When there I'll glare
It is like sun light inside rain"
"Even if I go, don't go
I'm telling you"
"It is possible to fly high
I'll continue and finish this"
"You don't change I have changed"
"There is no water inside moon"
"See the moon that sleeps in water"
"This kind of intoxication is not
good for you heart"
Why did you stop the car?
Shut up, you nag
They're checking all the cars
"The way I like, this world is
full of beauty in front of me"
Your son is kicking my tummy!
My baby!
"Tell me why are you dancing heart?"
Catch! Go rock it in a cradle
Excuse me?
Need details of this car
Thank you very much
Brother, found the car
Yes!
It crossed Toll 69
at 10 o clock this morning
One second, brother
Why are you standing here?
Sir, please wait
Just come this way I'll explain
-Let me go!
-There is no problem
Brother, it's been 4 hours
since the car crossed Toll 69
It's not crossed Toll 70 yet
So it's somewhere within this radius
I've stationed men at both the tolls
We can get them soon
We run inside by the count to ten!
Okay!
10!
You finish everything
before the count of ten?
What is it?
A room
Just for the night?
-Name?
-Khan
Khan what?
It's just Khan
No one gives their real name anyway
Two people
One key?
No, separate ones
Thank you
Let's go?
He doesn't even think
of me as a woman
Asked for two rooms
So insulting!
I knew it
What?
Madam, water?
Thanks
So spoilt!
Not a penny in his hands,
but he wants his own room!
You have the keys, right?
Shall I take them?
I won't touch you this time
Move your hand
Some more
Enough
No, that's enough
You!
Sorry
What sorry?
Saying sorry
after waking me up
Hey, doggie
You're so dead
Brother, there are 26 hotels
between Toll 69 and Toll 70
I've checked 20 of them
They haven't checked in there
There are 6 hotels left
Like Aruna Nivas, Dolphin Inn,
Hotel Crystal, and Navi Nivas
I'm going to check there now
Our guys are stationed
at both the tolls
If the car crosses the toll,
I'll be informed immediately
We can catch them by morning
Okay, I'll be in
Mussoorie by morning, too
We'll finish the deal
with both girls tomorrow
Who asked you to
roam around in the dark?
Why didn't you just go to sleep?
Such a pain!
I slipped
What can I do?
Lie down
Go on, lie down
You lie down
I'm scared, you stay here
Okay, I'll stay here
I'll sleep on the couch
Okay, okay
Move...a little bit
-Thanks
-For what?
For everything
Your alarm?
I'll kill you
Lie down!
Just asked
Go to sleep
You're the only person
I know who has an alarm to eat
You must love your mum's cooking
Can I tell you something?
I don't have parents
What?
When I was young
They died
I grew up and still live in a hostel
Know why this watch has an alarm?
If I don't go to eat on time,
the food at the mess would be over
If I tell him I am hungry,
the warden would cane me
I've been caned so many times,
you know
Hence, the alarm
Now it's become a habit
In this big world full of people,
there is not a single soul
To say
Hi How are you?
Being alone is so painful, you know?
But these two days I spent with you
I smiled more than I have all my life
Can I just be with you?
Forever?
You and I are one
Good night
Am I a little kid?
This is the day, man
Madam, the gentleman
has vacated the room
He asked me to give
this cover to you
Hi The place to deliver
the car is here So I'm going
You're returning to
Chennai tomorrow morning
Why?
I'm here on work!
You should leave
I don't know what kind
of place I'm headed to
It's not appropriate
to take you with me
I don't care
I'm going with you
You brat!
You wouldn't listen if I told you
So I had to leave this way
There is a ticket
to Chennai in this cover
I'll finish my job
and come to meet you
Sorry
And thanks
For everything
Careful
"Even then don't go
leaving me...Aahaa..."
Your son is kicking my tummy
Billy!
What are you doing here?
What's this?
Where's the girl?
Which girl?
The girl was the package?
Why didn't you tell me that before?
You had switched off your phone
How could we tell you?
Where is the girl now?
In her room
Hello?
I've seen him He is here with me
Did you kill him?
Thieving little
No
-Why?
-His phone was lost
Where is he?
-Right here In Mussoorie
He wouldn't have come to Mussoorie
if he intended to cheat us
He could have gone
off-course if he'd wanted to
You have a point
Let me talk to him
It's Dass
Hello?
Bond!
-You never answered our calls
-My phone was lost
You had called from a landline?
I was so worried,
I didn't answer any calls
Be quiet!
'It'll disturb the patient'
Bond, this is like a star hotel!
What are you doing?
Need to put drops in the eye
Dass?
How do you give her food?
Through the tube Twice everyday
Listen, Dass
Looks like she's staring right at me
Isn't she like a doll?
-Hello
-What is this?
Who are all these people?
Why have you entered
with your slippers?
Sister, you didn't tell them?
You should shut up and do
the job you've been paid to do
Pull some stunt and
you're done for
Look, Bond
If you finish this deal,
your sister is my sister
Get it?
25 years!
I've struggled my
way to where I am now
I'm not going to let
you take it all away
Got it?
Hold on
Brother?
Dass, you idiot!
Where the hell are you?
Network problem, brother
I did try No call went through
Where is the driver?
Did he call?
Brother, the package is on the way
-No complications?
-None whatsoever I'll handle it
The package will reach you shortly
Don't worry
I'm in Mussoorie now
Ask him to meet me at the monastery
Bond, I know you're a good guy
But you don't know
how bad these guys are
Just hand over the package,
collect the money and come back
Get to work Go on
Give him a phone and
a bundle of cash Okay?
Bond, don't think too much
-Brother, where's the bus to Chennai?
-It's just departed
Excuse me
Left me all alone Didn't you?
Why have you come back now?
Shakee
-Look
-Don't say anything
It's okay
"Even then don't go
leaving me...Aahaa..."
Never leave me again?
Promise?
You've promised over
your own head
Break it, and you'll
be in trouble
Don't get down till I tell you
Mr Bond?
Dass sent you?
May I know why you
kidnapped the girl?
If I'd turned my car around,
not a soul could have caught up
But I didn't do that
You trusted me with a job
I've finished it
I've taken my pay
Our deal is over
Now
I'll offer you a deal
Extra
I want that girl
Yesterday, if you'd touched the girl,
I'd have smashed you
But today,
I'll kill you for it
Wow!
This place is so beautiful
Quick
Give it
No! Wait
Careful
Nothing to worry
Give me your shirt
Pappu
Are you okay?
Lift him up
Give your shirt!
-Are you okay?
-Take him to the hospital
What's going on here?
Go! Quick
Get going
You too, go away
I don't need anybody
This is great
Let go
Where will you go now?
The game is just about to begin
Just the beginning
If you hit me
Think it's over?
I'm just an agent, like Dass
This is not just about money
It's bigger than you think
Do you know where she's going?
Durga Ghat
Do you know who
asked for this girl?
She's getting away
Get her
DAKSHA BHAI!
Give it
He's getting away
Let him go
Don't aim for where he is
Aim for where he is going to be
Let him go
Where are they now?
I spoke to Pooran Singh
They should be here anytime
He said that half an hour back
Call him
The phone is ringing
Who are you?
Tell me, sir
How did you get here?
I am
Welcome home
Help yourself to these sweets
-Help yourself
-Thanks
I thought they'd bash us up
But here's a welcoming ceremony!
Pooran Singh was supposed to
deliver the girl Why are you here?
Pooran Singh is your man?
I didn't know
He touched the girl;
I hit him
That's all
So
You're offering me 15 You
must have offered him a lot more, huh?
Why don't you pay me
the whole amount?
I did deliver the girl
safely Right?
Do you know why we
had this girl brought here?
I don't need to know that
All I need is money
For how long have
you worked with Dass?
Let's say
About six
I'll call Dass
Hello
Who do you think you are?
You hit him?
I'm fine, brother
How is the missus?
Are you mocking me?
I have never been known
to sheath a dry sword
I've got your salary, mind you
Oh yes, tell me!
You hit the agent and kidnap the girl
Think it's over?
That girl was Dhaksha Bhai
had asked for
Yes, he's right here
Just a minute - Give him the phone
-It's Dass
-I'll talk to him
-Dass?
-Yes Brother?
The girl was delivered on time
Good
The girl has reached?
I'm sending the payment
through your man
I'll collect it, brother
Okay, brother
Let me just talk to Bond
Thanks
Brother?
Bond, what are you doing there?
How's the weather at home?
Listen, that's a dangerous place
You enter once,
you'll never come back out
Really?
Super
I am serious
They've kidnapped a girl
from one corner of India to another
I need to find out why
I won't leave until then
Okay?
Listen to me
You're just a driver
You've given me
directions until now
Hereon, I make my own roads
Just shut up and sit in the backseat
I left my coat in the car
Ask him if it's safe?
Think about your sister
Sister?
Are you threatening me?
Go on
Talk to her
Don't worry
Thank you, Doctor
I'll take care
I moved her
When?
The fish is gone too?
There are 216 hospitals in Tamil Nadu
Try tracking her down
and take care of her
Wouldn't a man who cares
as much for his sister
Go all the way to protect her?
Should anything happen to her
Just a count to ten
You'll be done for
Hello Come here
Super, brother
Convey my regards to your wife
It's an imported coat
Cost me 7,500 rupees
Get lost!
I'm done talking
So the girl doesn't
know she's been kidnapped?
No
According to her,
I'm here to drop the car off
That's all
One minute
-It looks good, right?
-Yes
We're leaving?
See
I would leave now,
but she'd want to come with me
Having seen your welcome ceremony for her,
I suspect you'd want things to smooth
Do whatever you want with her
That isn't any of my concern
But things would be a
lot easier if I stick around
Also, this is not a part of the original
package This will cost you extra
Pay me a big one per day
I'll get it done in two days
We know what we're doing Quiet
Well, you
Are we leaving?
Yes
We're here, we've dropped the car off
Now, we're sorting out the payment
If it's finished,
we'll leave
You're our guests here
There is a festival coming up
Everything will be finished
in two days You must stay
Ravi Show them their rooms
What do they want with her?
Maybe she has a rare blood
group Some organ of hers?
What are you thinking?
Do you have a brain?
Not a chance
Maybe something about
your birth stars?
Your future husband destined to rule?
Or something like that?
-Do you want to?
-So, it's not that either!
What is it about you
You have short term memory loss?!
Do you forget everything
in fifteen minutes?
Why are you all smiles?
-Is the deal done?
-Of course
You got paid 15 million
just to deliver a car from Chennai?
Yes
So it's not just the car
There must have been something in it?
I won't ask you what it is,
but this is the last time
Yesterday, you were something else
Today you're everything to me
Want to give a kiss?
Kiss me
You've got vermillion on
your forehead What do we do?
You slept here all night?
Did something happen?
Fool!
Have you been here before?
Where?
North India
Yeah right
Never even crossed North of our city
What could it be?
Maybe
Saw that?
Come here
I got it for you
Always in such a hurry
I'd have shown you anyway
Isn't it nice?
Yeah Very nice
Welcome My guests!
Join us here
Come dine with us
Come on
-Where's Ravi?
-He's coming, brother
Ask everyone to come
I think it's their traditional attire
Maybe their family attire?
Your mother?
My grandmother
-How old is she?
-96 or 97
97?
Woah!
Can I feed her?
In our custom,
women are our Goddesses
They are our leaders
Our decision makers
It's called Rani Theni dynasty
Granny has been our leader
for the past two generations
After granny
Are there only male
children in your family?
There was a female child
Not anymore
She even smells like her
What is she saying?
She mistook you for someone else
One minute Be right back
So Uncle, is the job done?
The bail has been rejected
Everybody
Inside now You can eat later
Go on
Can't you hear us?
Sorry
Go
Awesome gravy!
Nice
I hate a meal interrupted
So you don't want to be heard!
You're telling me NOW
that the parole was rejected?
Idiot
We've been planning for months
Don't you know how
vital this parole is?
They refuse to give parole
to death row convicts
That's not my problem!
Break into the prison then
Break in, if you must
I need this done
While this girl is still here
Maybe we should try a bit harder
The court has rejected
our reason for parole
Listen
Apply for the parole now
We will get it
Do you need a better reason?
I've got all the info you asked for
There is a constant clash between
these two castes in Uttarakhand
The lower caste people submitted
a petition to build a school
Displeased, the higher caste people
Butchered forty of
the lower caste in retaliation
What happened?
The parole was rejected
Court refused to permit a death row
convict on parole to celebrate a festival
They say it's not a valid reason
What is your reason for parole now?
When did it happen?
Open up
The parole has been granted
We'll leave in another two hours
I'm at the prison now
Who will lead our family after you?
A girl child was born into
our family after two generations
She, too, is in the prison for trying
to preserve our family's honour
The one who slaughtered Was a woman
Called Gaggi Moi
I don't have a choice, Mother
Please understand
I thought you said
the parole was rejected
How did we get it?
It's Mother
What about Mother?
She's passed away
She was in a wheelchair all this time
Now she'll hang from
the wall on a photograph
Why do you feel so sad?
She wasn't your mother
You shall not kill anyone!
They are all mine to kill
Must bathe granny after
the meal, right?
Yes
If grandma looks at us-
What happened, grandma?
Granny!
Granny, what's happened?
What have you done?
I won't let you go
-Phone call, brother
-Tell me
He made us run around the
city hunting every hospital
But he had just shifted
her to the floor above
Just say the word
I've got the entire
hospital surrounded
Uncle
How long can she be out on parole?
-Four hours
-Okay
So
The cops will bring our
sister from the prison
By the prisoner's train,
straight to the graveyard
How many cops will
accompany her in the train?
Around 30
So the four hours in the graveyard
is when we save our sister
You had asked for that girl's
ID and passport It's ready
What next?
When all the issues die down, our sister
will fly abroad in the girl's passport
All of you, got it?
Did you get it?
What is it, Mr Bond?
James Bond?
We've been planning
this for six months
You just turned up yesterday
You're still following
the route I mapped for you
Somehow, you did one thing right
You brought us the girl on time
We're letting you go just for that
Go
One second
What did you want
to play the girl's lover?
One hundred thousand a day Right?
Do you believe me now?
Is this true?
Is he telling the truth?
-I told you
-One minute
You tell me
So you weren't delivering the car?
You could have told me
I don't have anyone
No mother or father
to grieve my death
I thought I had one man
Now I've lost that, too
It's okay
You can take me
I know you'd do anything
for your sister
But you don't know what
I'd be willing to do for you
Start walking
Sit here
Your arm
I need to make a call
Last wish, huh?
Give him your phone
-Doctor
-Hello
Nandini's brother speaking
Tell me
If you don't mind
if you near my sister
I want to talk to my sister
Please pass on the phone?
Hello?
Talk to her
Hi, how are you doing?
I was to return sooner,
but this trip took unexpected turns
On my way here,
I saw this beautiful sunset in Agra
I'll take you there
when everything is okay
You'll definitely love it
She loved it, too
Shakee
She is a lot like you
Just like you,
I am all she has
On the way here, two strangers
died in a motorcycle accident
She was so disturbed
Today, she is on her way to die
She knows it, too
She's doing it for me
I'm going
I'm going to try to save the girl
I know you'll regain
consciousness someday
When you open your eyes,
if I stand before you
You'll find her by my side
I'll introduce you both
But when you open your eyes,
if I am not there
Do understand
That your brother tried
to save a girl like you
And failed
She can hear me talk
Call the Chief Doctor
immediately, Nurse
I can't believe it It's never
happened in this hospital before
Call the doctor
This is fantastic I never
thought Her eyes are watering!
I can't believe it
Stop Move away!
Doctor, please come immediately
This is fantastic
Come to the ward immediately
How far is the graveyard from here?
Sir, time is up
Take her away
I've asked the cop to kill this girl
Do it yourself if he fails
Okay, brother
Run away, or they'll kill you
Gadgi is trying to escape
Don't shoot
Catch her!
"Come what may..."
You won't leave me alone
here and go, right?
"Let anything happens..."
It's Gaggi, our enemy!
How dare she come here
after killing our people?
Kill her
Boss! I've saved our family's legacy
The townsfolk are on pursuit
You handle them
Take Gaggi away
Gaggi, go inside
Let go!
Our plans will go to waste
if the townsfolk catch sight of you
Go inside, first!
I said inside
Why are we going back?
What's wrong?
We can't run away from this
We need to end it here
Please
Don't go outside
Granny gave up her life for this
You'll ruin everything
Wuss
Catch her!
Shoot!
Bittu, what's happened to you?
Fire your gun
Let me go!
Go Faster
-Be alert, guards
-Yes, sir!
Come on!
They said you looked like me
You're ugly
Give me the gun
Gaggi tried to run from the cops
You stopped her
She shot you
And you shot her
Give me some time
Why? Is this not a
good time to die?
How long?
Ten seconds
Come on, brother
Go, "di"
Fool
Where are you going?
Let her go
It's all for her, right?
Gaggi!
Don't!
Where do you think you're going?
Dodo, can you fly?
It's all for her, right?
It's over
What?
Go straight
Me? I should drive?
Of course, you Go straight, 'di'
Fast!
Hit the brakes
Can't you see I'm talking?
Gadgi!
What should I do?
Reverse no, first gear
Okay, sir!
First gear Don't screw up!
That's really easy, sir
Superb!
Did I do well?
You did great
I should have reversed this way
Why did I do it wrong?
Normally, I don't make
the same mistake twice
Hey, Dodo!
Your mistake saved your life
Get down
And my license?
License
License?
I'll give your money back
Take this car
Take me, too
Look at that face!
Ride on cattle instead
No brakes or gears in it
Okay!
Okay, at least tell me now
What's your name?
Yuck!
Is that even a name?
Want to see my license?
Good for me
-= www.OpenSubtitles.org =-